<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Orbituses on Orbitus Robotics</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/orbitus/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Orbituses on Orbitus Robotics</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 11:10:36 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/orbitus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Orbitus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/orbitus/orbitus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 11:10:36 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/orbitus/orbitus/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;rodolfo-aramayo&#34;&gt;Rodolfo Aramayo&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;senior-iosmacos-developer&#34;&gt;Senior iOS/macOS Developer&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am a developer for macOS/iOS/watchOS/VisionOS. I have&#xA;dedicated all my time and resources throughout my professional&#xA;career to perfecting my craft of delivering amazing software with&#xA;Swift, SwiftUI and Objcetive-C. I was on the Apple hardware team&#xA;writing and debugging automation tools infrastructure in order to&#xA;facilitate the testing of the latest products to the world. I have had the&#xA;privilege to work with the most powerful frameworks ever created for&#xA;the Apple ecosystem and am honored to have had a chance to touch&#xA;the insides of these devices for over 2.6 years. Before this I worked&#xA;with the Apple Store app and Caffé Macs in my previous positions&#xA;at Apple. I delivered some of the most cutting edge AR experiences&#xA;ranging from Sports Illustrated, AR cinema experiences for movies&#xA;like Ready Player One, and even AR Experiences for Comopolitan.&#xA;I try to hone my craft by working on my passion project, R.O.B. A&#xA;droid that utilizes a Mac mini in order to test my realtime software&#xA;engineering skills along with my mechanical engineering skills. I&#xA;have always tried to push the boundaries of AR and Robotics. I have&#xA;been to MakerFaire multiple times with my droid and strive to inspire&#xA;and encourage young engineers to live their dreams and enjoy the&#xA;love and excitement of writing code that moves and talks with the&#xA;latest LLM models like ChatGPT and Gemini. I am a father of 7&#xA;children and a husband to a wonderful wife. Please follow our droid&#xA;on social media&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
